PAUL KENNETH KENT

Bicester, United Kingdom | pkennethkent@gmail.com

I've worked in multiple technical roles gaining a wealth of experience. My passion is software development where I've contributed value across the stack. I believe I am natural leader who is able to step into leadership roles when required.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | DIFFBLUE | NOVEMBER 2017 - NOVEMBER 2018

Built and maintained internal product dashboard systems that analysed the results of our AI driven test generation software.

DEVELOPMENT TEAM LEAD | DIFFBLUE | NOVEMBER 2018 - JUNE 2020

Expanding on my previous role I was tasked with leading a team of developers to build a pipleline that analysed 1000s of open repositories. The aim was to gather feedback on the quality of the tests produced.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | VENTURE HARBOUR | JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2022

I joined an exciting team of engineers with aim to plan, build and maintain multiple ventures at a rapid pace. As the team was small, we worked on all area of the technical stack with my primary focus on backend system - postgres, api, oauth and graphql

LEAD ENGINEER | VENTURE HARBOUR | SEPTEMBER 2022 - JANUARY 2023

I became a Lead Engineer to work on our most ambitious venture (truenorth.io). I worked closely with the product team and my team of engineers to deliver a highly polished product.

EDUCATION

OXFORD BROOKES UNIVERSITY | OXFORD | SEPTEMBER 2005 - SEPTEMBER 2010

Computer Science and Multimedia Systems - 2:1

CASTLE SCHOOL SECONDARY & 6TH FORM | BRISTOL | SEPTEMBER 1997 - JULY 2005

Grades A - C

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Javascript | Java | Typescript | Unit Tests | Docker | Kubernetes | git | React | Project Planning | Agile | GCP | GraphQL | NextJS | Auth | Postgres | e2e testing | Prisma | SQL



